威尔 · 森塔斯: “大家好，这就是过去两天的惊人工作。”。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: So folk, there it is,
amazing work over the last two days.
对我在整个过程中号召的每一个人都表示深深的感谢。
Enormous gratitude to every single person
that I called upon the whole way through.
谁知道你是否知道这一天的到来。
Who knows if you knew that was coming.
但是我的天哪，如果你不知道的话，(笑)这是一次怎样的旅行。
But my goodness if you did not know,
[LAUGH] what a ride it's been.
但这绝对是一种乐趣。
But it's been an absolute pleasure.
我们来简单总结一下。
We went through, let's briefly sum it up.
我们学习了 JavaScript 的基本原理,
We went through the underlying
principles of JavaScript that you saw,
他们没有离开。
they never went away.
(笑)他们在岩床上。
[LAUGH] They were at bedrock.
然后我们看到了一个有趣的片段，它构成了函数的核心部分
We then saw an interesting piece that
makes up a core part of functional
编程，我们的高阶函数，这种能力留下一个占位符
programming, our higher order functions,
that ability to leave a placeholder for
一些功能的函数，然后才确定的功能完全
some functionality in a function and then
only determine the functionality fully
这是函数式编程的一部分。
once we run the function and that's pretty
nice, part of functional programming.
或者我甚至可以告诉你，你可以把这些东西带到哪里去。
Or maybe I'll even say actually
where you can take these things.
如果你想了解更多，因为有很多函数你可以
If you wanna learn more about that,
because there's a ton of functions you can
编辑，特别是最强大的一个，减少，其实挺漂亮的,
edit, particularly the most powerful one
of all, reduce, pretty beautiful actually,
所有在功能性编程霍尔部分。
all in the functional
programming Hall parts.
我会告诉你一些关于这里的事情。
I'll give you some little
follow on things here.
然后我们解决了对我来说 JavaScript 最美妙的特性，因为它就是
Then we solve what for me is the most
beautiful feature of JavaScript, cuz it's
像这样，哇，如果我得到了这个，我真的得到了 JavaScript 的执行模型。
like the kinda, wow, if I get that,
I truly get JavaScript's execution model.
一个函数实际上可以将保存的代码返回到另一个全局
The idea that a function could in fact
return saved code into another global
标签，这将带来与它的数据
label and
that that's gonna bring data with it on
他的背包我们就可以永久地拿到了,
his backpack that we then have access
to for the rest of time, permanently,
你会发现你可以在任何地方使用它。
you will discover you
can use that everywhere.
在我们不知情的情况下，它主宰了工作。
That dominates jobs
without us even knowing.
然后我们在事件循环中看到了异步 JavaScript。
Then we saw Asynchronous JavaScript
in the event loop.
这是我喜欢做一个更深入的潜水，就像我们看到了整个
This is something I'd love to do
a deeper dive like we saw the whole
实际上，我们已经远远超越了 JavaScript。
model of asynchronous JavaScript, well,
honestly, we went way beyond JavaScript.
这是运行在 web 浏览器中的 JavaScript，所以我们不得不引入所有的浏览器
It was JavaScript running in the web
browsers, so we had to bring in all
这里的其他东西是 JavaScript 提供给我们访问的。
the other stuff down here that
JavaScript gives us access to.
他们有一大堆规则来规定这些东西在网络上完成时的方式
And they have a bunch of rules for
how that stuff when it finishes in the web
浏览器，就像对互联网老前辈说话一样,
browser, like speaking to
the Internet old timers,
允许它的相关功能，它将在完成时运行。
allows its associated functionality
that it's gonna run on completion.
从背景工作中得到的数据,
And the data that maybe came
back from that background work,
回到 JavaScript。
back into JavaScript.
有一些后续的东西围绕着这些东西，如链接承诺,
There's some follow on things from that
around things like chaining promises,
其他领域，自己从零开始构建承诺。
other areas, constructing
promises from scratch yourself.
但是有趣的是接下来。
But interesting to follow on into.
最后，我们看到了类，原型，原型链,
And then finally, we saw here classes,
prototypes, the prototype chain,
不是原型属性的原型属性,
the proto property that is
not the prototype property,
但是链接到了原型的属性。
[LAUGH] but
does link to the prototype property.
我们看到了新的和条款是如何没有改变任何东西的引擎盖下除了
We saw how new and clause are not
changing anything under the hood besides
自动化和给我们一个速记的方式，实现我们直接取得的成就
automating and giving us a shorthand way
of achieving what we achieved directly
使用 object.create，在我们的解决方案2中手动细粒度控制。
with object.create, manually fine-grained
control in our solution two.
我们看到这个关键词和所有有趣的，或者
We saw that this keyword and
all the interesting, or
两种有趣的解决方式。
the two interesting
ways that it works out.
我们看到了箭头函数可以给我们更多的控制,
We saw how arrow functions can give
us even more control over that,
这个关键词把我们带到了最后一部分,
this keyword, and took us all
the way through to the final part,
这是建立从零开始，使用所有这些零件的引擎盖下的阶级。
which was building out class from scratch
using all of these pieces under the hood.
朋友们，这绝对是一种乐趣。
So folk, it's been an absolute pleasure.
我喜欢和你们一起做这件事。
I've loved doing this with all of you.
我想就是这样了。
I think that is it.
假设我们收工了，5:30，我们成功了。
Let's say we're a wrap, 5:30, we did it.
很高兴认识你。
It's been a pleasure.
总有一天我们会再见到你们的。
We will see you all [LAUGH] one day again.
谢谢大家，干杯。
Thank you everybody and cheers.
讲者2: 太好了。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Great.
(掌声)
[APPLAUSE]